A Guide to the Robert Young Clay Papers, 1789-2010 (bulk 1920-2007)
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Clay Family Research Files., Extent: 97 boxes. (Box 1-97)
  - Subseries F. Allied Families (A-Z)., Extent: 23 boxes. (Box 45-67)
    The Allied Families (A-Z) subseries also includes genealogical research on numerous families related to the Clay family. There is a substantial amount of material on the Cabaniss, Filmer, Green, Jenkins, Jones, Parker, Pride, and Watkins families.
    - Abbott. (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Abbott, Lydia Clay. (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - Adams. J.T.. (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Adams, Joel T. (and others). (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - Adams, Mollie Litchfield. (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - Adams, Mourning - Albemarle County, VA. (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - Adams, Robert. (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - Agee. (Box 45, Folder 27)
    - Agee, James (Knoxville Birthplace). (Box 45, Folder 28)
    - Akin. (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - Akin, James. (Box 45, Folder 30)
    - Allen of Beechwood. (Box 45, Folder 31)
    - Allen, Daniel. (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Allen, Wyatt Wilson Jr.. (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Allen-Clay - Amelia County, VA. (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Allen-Clay (David C. Allen's Notes). (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Allin. (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Amonett. (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Amos. (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Argall. (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Austen. (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Avery. (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Baber. (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Bailey. (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Baird, Major. (Box 46, Folder 13-14)
    - Baker. (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Balote, Henry. (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Barker - Washington County, VA. (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Barksdale. (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Barnwell. (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Bartley. (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Bashinsky, Lizzie Burford. (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Bass. (Box 46, Folder 22-23)
    - Bass, Jeremiah. (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Battersby. (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Beasley. (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Beasley, Sue D.. (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Bedford. (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Bedinger, Henrietta Clay. (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Bedwell. (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Belcher. (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Belcher, Francis 13466. (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Belcher, Richard. (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Belote. (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Bennett, Howard. (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Bennin. (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Bentley. (Box 47, Folder 14-16)
    - Bentley of Virginia. (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Bernard. (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Berry. (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Best. (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Bevill. (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - Bibb. (Box 47, Folder 22-23)
    - Bidgood. (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Bilbo. (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - Birch. (Box 47, Folder 26)
    - Blakemore. (Box 47, Folder 27)
    - Blankenship. (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Bloodworth. (Box 47, Folder 29-30)
    - Blumberg, Natalie. (Box 47, Folder 31)
    - Bondurant. (Box 47, Folder 32)
    - Borden. (Box 47, Folder 33)
    - Borum. (Box 47, Folder 34)
    - Bouldin. (Box 47, Folder 35)
    - Bowry. (Box 47, Folder 36)
    - Boykin. (Box 47, Folder 37)
    - Branch, Olive. (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Bransford. (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Brantly. (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Brasier. (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Bratten. (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Bratton. (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Brewster. (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Bridgewater. (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Brigance. (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Brimm. (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Broadway. (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Brooks. (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Brooks, Robert - Mecklenburg County, VA. (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Browder. (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Brown. (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Bruce. (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Brumfield, Eleanor Clay - Tazewell County, VA. (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Bryant. (Box 48, Folder 18-19)
    - Bryant - Brunswick County, VA and NC. (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - Bryant (Huguenot). (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - Buchanan. (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - Buckner. (Box 48, Folder 23)
    - Burfoot. (Box 48, Folder 24)
    - Burford. (Box 48, Folder 25)
    - Burgamy. (Box 48, Folder 26)
    - Burns, David. (Box 48, Folder 27)
    - Burrell, Ruth Clay. (Box 48, Folder 28)
    - Butler. (Box 48, Folder 29)
    - Butts, Benjamin H.. (Box 48, Folder 30)
    - Byrd, William (and Carter). (Box 48, Folder 31)
    - Cabaniss. (Box 48, Folder 32-34)
    - Cabaniss. (Box 49, Folder 1-6)
    - Cadet-LeGros. (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Cage. (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Callaway. (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Calvet. (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Campbell, Mary Elizabeth. (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Cannon. (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Canter. (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Carloss. (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Carson. (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Carter. (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Chaffin, Nathan. (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Chambon/Jambon. (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Chapman. (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Chappell. (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Chastaine. (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - Cheatham. (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - Cheatham, Leonard. (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - Chewning. (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Chiles. (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Christian. (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Christian, Charles. (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Christian-Prosser. (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Christopher. (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Claiborne. (Box 50, Folder 7-9)
    - Clark, Christopher. (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Clark, Christopher/Johnson. (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Cleaton, Delphie Clay. (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Clement, Frank G.. (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Clements. (Box 50, Folder 14-15)
    - Clements, Dorothy 13432 2. (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Clements, William. (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Clements, William R.B.. (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Clemons. (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Cobbs. (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Cochran. (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Cocke. (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Cole. (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Cole, Dorothy Clay 1344. (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Coleman. (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Coleman, John G.. (Box 50, Folder 26)
    - Cook. (Box 50, Folder 27)
    - Cooksey. (Box 50, Folder 28)
    - Corker. (Box 50, Folder 29)
    - Corley/Burford. (Box 50, Folder 30)
    - Cornwell. (Box 50, Folder 31)
    - Cotton. (Box 50, Folder 32)
    - Cousins. (Box 51, Folder 1-2)
    - Cousins, Robert - Amelia County, VA. (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Covington. (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Cox. (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Cox of Dixon Springs. (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Craig. (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Craig, Pete. (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Crain. (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Cralle. (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Crawford, Mary Clay. (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Creekmore. (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Crenshaw. (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Cronk. (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Crowder. (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Culbreath. (Box 51, Folder 16-17)
    - Cunningham. (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Dabney. (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Dammeron. (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Daniel. (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Darnell/Darnall. (Box 51, Folder 22-24)
    - David. (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - Davis. (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Davis, Braxton. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Davis/Craig. (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Day. (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Dearing. (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Dearing - Campbell County, VA. (Box 169, Folder 9-10)
    - Dearing - Campbell County, VA. (Box 170, Folder 8)
    - DeBow. (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Demonbreun. (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Dennis. (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Dickinson - Franklin County, VA. (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Dill. (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Dillon. (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Dixon, Tilman. (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Dodge. (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Donoho. (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Dorris. (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Dorsey. (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Dotson. (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - D'Sassin. (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Dumas. (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Dupree. (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Dupuy. (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - Durant. (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - Dutoit. (Box 52, Folder 23-25)
    - DuVal. (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Early. (Box 52, Folder 27)
    - Edmondson. (Box 52, Folder 28)
    - Elder. (Box 52, Folder 29)
    - Embry. (Box 52, Folder 30)
    - English. (Box 52, Folder 31)
    - Epes, Laban. (Box 52, Folder 32)
    - Epsey/Askey/etc.. (Box 52, Folder 33)
    - Ewing. (Box 52, Folder 34)
    - Ezell. (Box 52, Folder 35)
    - Fanning. (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Farley. (Box 53, Folder 2-3)
    - Farley-Winfrey-Watkins-Booth. (Box 53, Folder 4-5)
    - Farmer. (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Fearn. (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Ferguson/Farguson. (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Filmer. (Box 53, Folder 9-14)
    - Filson. (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Finney. (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Fitch. (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Fleshman, Betsy (Mrs. Howard McCord). (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Forcee. (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Foster. (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Foster, Peter. (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Frame. (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Franklin. (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Franklin, Isaac - Sumner County, TN. (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Franklyn, Thomas - Chesterfield County, VA. (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - French. (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Friend. (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Gann. (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Garrett. (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Garrett, Odell. (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Garrett, Dr. Sam Y.. (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Gates. (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Gibbs. (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Golden. (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Goode. (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Goolsby. (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Gore. (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Gory. (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Graves. (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Graves, Charles. (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Graves, Charles Clay. (Box 54, Folder 26-27)
    - Green. (Box 54, Folder 28-29)
    - Green. (Box 55, Folder 1-8)
    - Green, Col. Abraham. (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Green, Amey Clay. (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Green, Filmer. (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Green, Filmer - Henry County, VA. (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Green, Marston - Amelia County, VA. (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Green, Obedience - Amelia County, VA. (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Green, Thomas - Amelia County, VA. (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Green, Thomas and wife Hannah - Family Tree (Map-case 56, Drawer 5)
    - Green, William - Amelia County, VA. (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Green (Other Families). (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Green/Clay (Mrs. Morton's Notes). (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Green/Williamson. (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Gregory. (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Guerrant. (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Gwaltney. (Box 56, Folder 7-9)
    - Gwaltney - Smith County, TN. (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Gwin. (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Gwyn - Sumner County, TN. (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Hackett. (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Hamilton. (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Hamilton (John Lee Swaney). (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Harding. (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Harding - Lunenburg County, VA. (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Hardyshell. (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Hargis. (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Harper. (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - Harper. (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Harwood. (Box 57, Folder 1a)
    - Haskins - Mecklenburg County, VA. (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Hatcher. (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Haun. (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Haynie. (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Hayslip. (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Henderson. (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Henderson, Martha "Patsy". (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Herod. (Box 57, Folder 9-10)
    - Herod, William - Smith County, TN. (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Hesson. (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Hickey. (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Hickey/Shivers. (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Hightower. (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Hite. (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Hite-McLean-Hardy-Kimbrough. (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Hobson. (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Hodges. (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - Hodges - Franklin County, VA. (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - Hood. (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - Houston. (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - Hudson - Amelia County, VA. (Box 57, Folder 23)
    - Hughes. (Box 57, Folder 24)
    - Hunt. (Box 57, Folder 25)
    - Hurley. (Box 57, Folder 26)
    - Ingram, Moses. (Box 57, Folder 27)
    - Jacob. (Box 57, Folder 28)
    - Jeffreys. (Box 57, Folder 29)
    - Jenkins. (Box 57, Folder 30-31)
    - Jenkins. (Box 58, Folder 1-3)
    - Jett. (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Jevodan. (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Johnson, James - Revolutionary War. (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Johnson, Philip. (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Johnston. (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Jolley. (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Jones. (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Jones-Clay. (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Jones (Jouany). (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Jones, Lucy Clay 13529. (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Jones, Mordecai. (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Jones of Fork. (Box 58, Folder 15-16)
    - Jones, Reps. (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Jones, Robert R.. (Box 58, Folder 18-19)
    - Jones, Thomas and Susannah. (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - Jordan (North Carolina). (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - Keen. (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Keen - Henry County, VA. (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Keene, William. (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Kemp. (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Kenner, Rodham. (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Kimbrough. (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - King. (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Kirkpatrick. (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - LaBarrear. (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - LaForce. (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - LaFuite. (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - LaPrad. (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Lea. (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - LeFevre. (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - LeGrand. (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - LeGros. (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Lewis. (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Lewis, Hopkins. (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Lipscomb. (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Lockado. (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Lockett. (Box 59, Folder 21-22)
    - Logwood. (Box 59, Folder 23)
    - Loving. (Box 59, Folder 24)
    - Lowry. (Box 59, Folder 25-27)
    - Lumpkin. (Box 59, Folder 28)
    - Lumpkin, Moore. (Box 59, Folder 29)
    - Lynch. (Box 59, Folder 30)
    - Magann. (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Magill. (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Mallet. (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Mallory, James Baugh. (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Mallory, Robert Mason. (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Mangum. (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Markham. (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Marshall, Alexander. (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Marston. (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Martin. (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Martin/Clay. (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Martin of Halifax County, VA. (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Martin (Huguenots). (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Martin, Col. William (Dixon Springs). (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Mason - Greensville County, VA. (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Mason, John Young. (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Mason (Young). (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Maxey. (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Maxey - Franklin County, VA. (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - McCord. (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - McDonald. (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - McGlasson. (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - McKenna, Patrick - Charts. (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - McMahan-Bird (Pollyanna Creekmore). (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - McMurtry. (Box 60, Folder 25)
    - Meade of Amelia County. (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Meador of Isle of Wight County. (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Meredith. (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Meredith, Rice - Amherst County, VA - Will, 1787. (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Metcalf. (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Milburn. (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Miller. (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Mitchell. (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Moody. (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Morell, Pat. (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Morgan, Joshua. (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Morris. (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Morton. (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Moseley. (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Moseley (Green Descendants). (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Mountcastle. (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Mountcastle - Charles City County, VA. (Box 61, Folder 16a)
    - Muns. (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Murray, Alexander (m. Elizabeth Marvell Clay). (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Murrey of Buckingham County, VA. (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Mustain. (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Nash. (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - Newman, Richard. (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Nunnally. (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - Old. (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - Oliver. (Box 61, Folder 25)
    - Orange. (Box 61, Folder 26)
    - Osborne. (Box 61, Folder 27)
    - Ostein. (Box 61, Folder 28)
    - Owen, James Welch. (Box 61, Folder 29)
    - Page. (Box 61, Folder 30)
    - Parham. (Box 61, Folder 31)
    - Paris. (Box 61, Folder 32)
    - Parker. (Box 61, Folder 33-35)
    - Parker. (Box 62, Folder 1-2)
    - Parker. (Box 169, Folder 13)
    - Parker (Hendrick). (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Parker of Halifax County (Drucilla). (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Parker, Richard - Goochland County, VA Ordinary License, 1743. (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Parker, Thomas - Goochland County, VA. (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Paschall. (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Patton. (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Patton, Andrew. (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Patton - North Carolina. (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Peachy, Thomas G.. (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Pearis. (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Perrow. (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Peters. (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Poland. (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Porter. (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Povall. (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Powell. (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Powell, Mary of Amelia County. (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Pride. (Box 62, Folder 20-22)
    - Pride (Donald Shipp). (Box 62, Folder 23)
    - Halcott Pride of Sussex. (Box 62, Folder 24)
    - Pritchett. (Box 62, Folder 25)
    - Proctor. (Box 62, Folder 26-27)
    - Proctor of Wilson County, TN. (Box 62, Folder 28)
    - Proctor/Hill/Scurlock/Farguson. (Box 63, Folder 1-2)
    - Prosser. (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Pryor. (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Quisenberry of Carroll and Floyd Counties, VA. (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Rankin. (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Rapeen. (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Ratledge. (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Reed. (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Reel. (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Reese. (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Richmond. (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Ridgeway. (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Robertson. (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Robey. (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Robinson. (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Roby. (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Rochet. (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Rogers. (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - Rowlett. (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - Rucks. (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Rudd. (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - Ruffin. (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - Russell. (Box 63, Folder 24)
    - Sadler. (Box 63, Folder 25)
    - Sallee. (Box 63, Folder 26)
    - Saunders. (Box 63, Folder 27)
    - Saunders of Bledsoeboro. (Box 63, Folder 28)
    - Scot. (Box 63, Folder 29)
    - Scurlock. (Box 63, Folder 30)
    - Seay-Vaughn. (Box 63, Folder 31)
    - Shacklett. (Box 63, Folder 32)
    - Shivers. (Box 63, Folder 33)
    - Sibley. (Box 63, Folder 34)
    - Singleton. (Box 63, Folder 35)
    - Sircy. (Box 63, Folder 36)
    - Snead. (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Snell. (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Snell (Amelia Clays). (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Snellings. (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Snoddy. (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Soblet/Sublet. (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Soper. (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Soper (Paul Riggs Notes). (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Souille. (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Southall, William B.. (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Spangler. (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Speight. (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Stanley. (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Stanley, Dancey. (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Stanly, Edward m. Hannah Wilson Clay. (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Starr. (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Stewart. (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Stewart, Mary Clay. (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Stewart - Henrico County, VA. (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Stewart, John - Henrico County, VA. (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Stone. (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Stovall (Old Documents). (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Sullivan, Daniel m. Cynthia Clay. (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - Summers. (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - Swaney. (Box 64, Folder 25)
    - Swaney (John Lee Swaney). (Box 64, Folder 26)
    - Swinney, Phebe Cabaniss Belcher 13466. (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Sydnor, Floyd. (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Sydnor, Richard B. Jr.. (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Tanner. (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Tarry. (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Taylor. (Box 65, Folder 6-8)
    - Taylor - Sumner County, TN. (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Thackston/Thaxton. (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Thaxton. (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Thomas. (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Thomas, Edith Allen. (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Thompson, Billy B.. (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Thweat. (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Tinsley. (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Trabue. (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Trigger. (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Tucker. (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Tucker, Matthew. (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Tucker, Robert - Amelia County, VA. (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Tuke, Sir Brian. (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Turney. (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Turpin. (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - Vigue/Lavigue. (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - Vinson. (Box 65, Folder 25a)
    - Waller. (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - Walthall. (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - Ward. (Box 65, Folder 28)
    - Watkins. (Box 65, Folder 29-30)
    - Watkins. (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Watkins - Louisa County, VA. (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Watkins-Curd-Smith. (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Watkins, Henry W. - Powhatan County, VA. (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Watkins, Joseph and Mary - Chesterfield County, VA. (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Watkins, Joseph - Chesterfield County, VA. (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Watkins, Philip. (Box 66, Folder 6a)
    - Watkins, Philip - Lunenburg County, VA. (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Watkins, Stephen. (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Watkins, Stephen D.. (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Watkins, Thomas. (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Watkins, Thomas (m. Mary Clay?). (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Watkins, Thomas Jr. - Henrico County, VA. (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Watson. (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Webster. (Box 66, Folder 14-15)
    - West. (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - West - Isle of Wight County, VA. (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - West, Robert. (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - West, Robert - Iredell County, NC. (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Westmoreland. (Box 66, Folder 20-22)
    - Wilburn. (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Williams (Prentiss Price Notes). (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Williamson, Amey Clay Green 1355. (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Wills. (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Wills, Philmer - Halifax County, VA. (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Wilson. (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Wilson - Amelia County, VA. (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Willson - Amelia County, VA. (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Winfree. (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Winn. (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Winston. (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Witcher. (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Witt. (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Wood, Paul. (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Woodall. (Box 67, Folder 15-17)
    - Woodall, John - Franklin County, VA. (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Woodson. (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Worsham. (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Wright. (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Wright-Burton. (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Wright, Michael m. Miriam Clay. (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - Yancey, Mary. (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - Zaruba. (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - Zimmerman. (Box 67, Folder 26)
  - Subseries G. Notebooks., Extent: 14 boxes. (Box 68-81)
    The Notebooks, or binders, contain the final typed group sheets with supporting documentation that were compiled from the family research files listed above. There are three groups of notebooks, and there is a "key" or listing of them. There is also an explanation of the system Clay used in numbering each individual. Some of the notebooks contain an index at the beginning, and some of them are missing. It is not clear whether these were combined with, or superceded by, other notebooks, or integrated into the family research files.
    - Key to Clay Family Notebooks. (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Volume 1 - First Five Generations. (Box 68, Folder 2-9)
    - Volume 2 - Isham Clay. (Box 69, Folder 1-3)
    - Volume 3 - John Clay. (Box 69, Folder 4-6)
    - Volume 4 - Cabaniss. (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Volume 5 - Obediah Clay. (Box 69, Folder 8-9)
    - Volume 6 - William Clay. (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Volume 7 - Mitchell Clay. (Box 69, Folder 11-13)
    - Volume 8 - Jesse Clay. (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Volume 10 - Dr. Henry Clay. (Box 70, Folder 2-4)
    - Volume 11 - Charles Clay. (Box 70, Folder 5)